I position myself above, the brain does not go down to
there, I position myself above, roughly at the level of the insula, my
hands go here above, you see there, my thumbs cross and I need to
have a really good support with my elbows, my wrists on the table,
I get in like this, the touch is extremely light, okay, so
I am looking here.
And I slowly position myself on this field, you see,
and I wait to see.
So here, what I need to feel is do I have enough expansion?
First thing, I don’t have enough expansion.
I’m not pushed enough.
Do you think I was going to have good expansion right away?
I don’t have enough expansion.
We’re going to help it a little...
If I don’t have enough expansion, either I will look at the heart, or
I will check the digestive pathways.
If I don’t have enough, I will go up to the level of the sacrum, to the medullary level,
etc.
I will see where I can help to re-energize things.
Usually, with the heart.
mesenteric axes or splenic axis, that’s enough. I put it well here.
When there is expansion, I will exaggerate
the movement for didactic purposes. I
have an expansion and then I have a forward flexion movement like this.
It’s as if I’m bringing
the brain towards the heart.
Flexion, what do we call it?
Cranial.
Then behind, I need to have the possibility here, hop, I’m looking.
I have a slight deficit here behind.
I don’t quite have the correct movement in cervical flexion.
Certainly a cervical or structural correction is needed here.
I will bring this here already.
There, it passes very gently.
There, I’m paying more attention to my little fingers.
Okay?
Now, I am looking for pontine flexion.
There, I go down.
Okay?
Then I have a new expansion.
You see, in this expansion here, you can open my
hands like this, and then I have the entire tele-encephalization process, which
I recover at the occipital level, towards
the temporal level.
Oh.
Most errors are that I will look at that.
You do not touch a brain.
You are not under this frequency.
I position myself well above.
I do not touch with my thumbs.
So I still have a nice distance.
I get well here.
I do a full crew with my thumbs, very gently.
And an important support point here.
Here, there is good expansion.
We could compare.
expansion already here I can bring good
expansion meaning you
feel a wave of warmth and something that pushes
you
like this you see but here now I will make this movement very
gently
I have a support point here it’s not yet my each insular point
I made the forward flexion movement.
So now, it’s descending well, but it’s slightly twisting here.
Slightly, I accompany, very lightly in the left rotation.
Very lightly, she can feel it, perhaps a bit.
I am.
So here, there may have been, already at this stage,
we need to make a small correction.
That we will do at the cardiac level or I don’t know where.
We go down.
There, at some point, I have less of the perfect movement, but it’s okay.
And now, I can go towards the descent of cervical flexion.
She has to feel it.
There, there’s no problem, it’s going down.
We feel it quite strongly once we are in it.
Now, hop, I go to the pontine level.
There too, there will be a little something to do.
Now, I reposition myself, once I have the pontine level,
I refocus my attention on the tele-encephalic plane,
the teleencephalic openings.
And there, it should come towards me.
There, I have an expansion.
And there, I set myself on the H1.
Here, and that turns towards me, it expands, it rises.
And hop, it goes back.
And now, it goes down.
It expresses here, and now, I go down slowly,
into the great flexion, the large movement of tele-encephalization.
I recover this movement at the occipital level.
And...
You accompany this movement, you don’t impose it, you wait for it
to unfold and then you follow it.
But that means it’s there. I can place myself wherever I want, it’s still there. The rail is
drawn.
It has a particular rhythm.
No, it’s there. I just redo this pattern that is present.
And this pattern, it must at all times...
no cyclically it’s always there yes but what is it lasts for
this
day on the wrong line okay do you think it’s something
that reproduces like this okay no it’s not reproducible
before it’s not a practical system it’s a system that’s there it’s a
writing in ah yes I had forgotten we do embryology it’s as if the ears, well a bud of ears all this is being set up
yes it’s quite possible since at that moment
You will have the ocular system, the optic placode,
etc.
All that will appear.
There, I tell you, we will add the elements, but after.
Because if now I start to go in there,
I start to go into the ventricle and I start to talk about the median sulcus
with the dura mater appearing and the support point on such
a vessel, such a skull or such a vestige,
if you don’t want to go there. With this, you have
a line, we will add
some things, you see. Here, we will see
when we do this, here we will understand how
the ventricles are formed. Here, I understand
how the dura mater follows,
how the skull will form.
And suddenly, there’s something
that will block, I don’t know,
a level, you see there, I don’t know,
which one. I know the timing,
I know the synchro phenomenon,
you see, so I will go look for
an artery.
here. So he will feel, for example,
in his head, what is going to happen here. I will look for
an electrical level,
here. I will see if I go. It’s not easy
always to find.
There, I will put on top.
He can feel
what is happening up there.
That’s it,
It can work.
Here, or here.
It will be necessary to know the dynamics well.
Here I have an expansion that is, for example, a bit more important on the left side.
Try not to over-intellectualize your feeling,
because you are too busy putting too much electricity into the limbic system.
Expansion.
And soft, not complete, there you go, already
I am already moving towards flexion.
So here, good flexion.
But it has been a bit, not energized enough by the expansion.
There’s still another rhythm here, there you go, it moves forward, it tilts more to the left side.
I have
a little slowdown
it’s slower
the rhythm it is at
there for everyone
I can’t quite
connect with the
frontal lobe let's say
at the prosencephalic
the whole character area
This will require a small visceral work, I think, even urogenital.
She agrees, I now transition to function, to flexion.
It descends again, everything
is slowing down.
Okay, I reach the end there, hop, I go to the pontine system, there you go,
I have the ascension
of my tube, I become a support point, it pushes, there you go, pontine,
no problem,
it flows, in the vertebral expansion, very well on the right that
starts, stronger.
it starts to create the unfolding
I recover all that
I recover the bundle
down here
until
there you go
it flows well
there you go, great
So there was a bit of a sudden start, all at once, you
see, a little slow and then it’s well caught up.
it’s okay you can describe the change but
it’s true that at the beginning it was really as if it was
hard to get started letting go of something with more
fixation a bit
to the left and as if it couldn’t offer any expansion it’s true that the flexion
at first
is a little difficult and then when you make a connection I don’t know exactly where
Then I feel that it has unlocked the system.
And after, it can be as if at first, you are put at the
wheel of a Formula 1,
but you don’t know how to drive yet.
And then after, once you’ve learned a bit to drive, it works.
Yes, that’s it.
Environment, space, you let it breathe, you bask in it, you enter.
You go gradually and connect to that famous writing.
in the whole you center your listening at the level of the brain and if
it’s not okay you
I slightly observe elsewhere for me that’s it and then I will go see what
is happening as we will see later you have seen on this little diagram that
this little film that you like has a synchronicity in a bit of synchronism
I’m looking for the right word of synchronism sometimes there can
be
synchronicity.